let a = [
    {
        question: 'What should you do to get a full detailed picture of your finacial spending for the entire month',
        ans: 'To track where you are spending you money'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many months of expenses should you at least have, in case of an emergency',
        ans: '3 Months'
    },
    {
        question: 'What step should you complete before buying into a finacial plan.',
        ans: 'Know your money priorities'
    },
    {
        question: 'What rule holds true regardless of your current priority?',
        ans: 'Save Early and Often'
    },
    {
        question: 'Name three best side hustles mentioned in the article',
        ans: 'Blogging, Online Surveys, Becoming a virtual asasistant'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the recommended way of managing debts according to the article',
        ans: 'By paying of the debt with the highest interest rate.'
    },
    {
        question: 'What should you get no matter what stage of life you are in',
        ans: 'Life Insurance'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is one of the best money management tips related to getting a credit card',
        ans: 'Get a credit card with rewards'
    },
    {
        question: 'What should you do to avoid impulsive purchases?',
        ans: 'Wait at least 24 hours and then decide if you still want it'
    },
    {
        question: 'What are some of the most dependable classes to invest in?',
        ans: 'Stocks, bonds, Real estate'
    }
];

